Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Commerce, Science, Sports
    - - Commerce/Intervenor, 9/22/80
    - - Don't curb car imports, 12/12/80
    - - NASA appropriations, 7/30/81
    - - Responsible advertising, contraception, 3/17/82
  - Defense
    - - B-1 Bomber, 10/4/77
    - - U.S. Defense Posture, 6/26/78
    - - S. 870, amendment regarding Vietnam Vets, 1/23/80
    - - S. 870, amendment to veterans education, 2/4/80
    - - S.J. Res. 119, Vietnam Veterans War Memorial, 3/12/80
    - - H.J. Res. 521, Draft Registration, 6/11/80
    - - DOD Authorization, cutting Army Active Duty Strength, 7/1/80
    - - Defense budget, 9/4/80
    - - S. 3199, Herman Miller, Congressional Medal of Honor, 11/14/80
    - - S. 233, Herman Miller, Congressional Medal of Honor, 1/22/81
    - - AWACS, Arms sales to Saudi Arabia, 7/9/81
    - - MIA/POW, "Our Missing Americans", 7/29/81
    - - AWACS, 9/30/81, 10/5/81
    - - S. Res. 221, AWACS Resolution, 10/14/81
    - - AWACS letter, 10/28/81
    - - S.J. Res. 123, National Disabled Veterans Week, 11/10/81
    - - Disabled American Veterans, They Paid for Peace, 11/17/81
    - - START, Nuclear Defense, 11/19/81
    - - National Disabled Veterans Week, 12/11/81
    - - National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 5/5/82
    - - S. 2248, denying student financial benefits Amendment #1441, 5/12/82
    - - 747s vs. C-5, 5/13/82
    - - No Federal Aid for Students Scofflaws, 7/15/82
    - - Amendment #1441, Selective Service and Educational Benefits, 8/18/82
    - - Benjamin Sasway and Selective Service evasion, 9/23/82
    - - S. Con. Res. 131, MIA/POW, 12/3/82 (Box 28)
    - - Selective Svc. Reg., 12/16/82
    - - President Reagan's Program for economic recovery, 2/19/81
    - - Inflation article from Washington Post, 6/11/81
    - - New economic growth with onset of October 1, 9/30/81
    - - Enterprize zones, 3/30/82
  - Education
    - - S. 2142, Tuition Tax Relief Act, 3/8/78
    - - Bilingual Education, 5/1/79
    - - Opposition to student & parent loan programs, 12/11/80
    - - Bilingual Education, "Reagan & Two Tongues", 3/24/81
    - - Quotas and numerical ratios in higher education admissions, 5/21/81
    - - Bilingual Education hurts not helps, 10/14/81
    - - PTA membership month, 1/26/81
    - - City schools get a lesson in China's history, 12/11/81
    - - Abilities demonstrated by the disabled, 2/11/82
    - - Immigrants desire to learn English, 4/1/82
    - - Bilingual Education Improvements Act, 4/21/82
    - - Proposed cuts in Student Loan Programs, 4/27/82
    - - Bilingual Justice, 7/22/82
    - - Bilingual Education, Part I, 9/23/82
    - - Bilingual Education, Part II, 9/27/82
    - - Bilingual Education, Part III, 9/30/82
    - - Bilingual Education, Part IV, 9/30/82
    - - Bilingual Education, Part V, 10/1/82
  - Energy
    - - S. 2224, Solar Energy Bill, 1/25/80
    - - H.R. 3919, Windfall Profits Conference Report, 3/26/80
    - - S. 2532, reinstate oil leases, 4/2/80
    - - S. 2224, Solar energy, 5/20/80
    - - S. 2791, Palo Verde Electrical Power, 6/5/80
    - - Solar Plant near Barstow, 6/27/80
    - - Supplemental Appropriations, Amendment re DOE, 6/28/80
    - - Magnetic fusion, 9/23/80
    - - H.R. 5769, Energy Committee, 12/12/80
    - - H.R. 5769, Pauley roup, Santa Barbara, 12/12/80
    - - S. 506, Oil and gas leases, 2/19/81
    - - S. 700, amends Windfall Profits Tax Act, 3/12/81
    - - Outer continental Shelf, 6/9/81
    - - Clinch River Breeder Reactor Project, 11/5/81
    - - U.P. Amendment #674, Low-Income Home Energy Assistance, 11/19/81
    - - Solar Energy in California, 4/28/82
    - - S. 2773, Alaska Oil Bill, 7/26/82
    - - Big Sur and offshore leases, 12/14/82
  - Environment
    - - H.R. 3757, Channel Islands amendment re Santa Rosa Island, 2/18/80
    - - H.R. 3757, Channel Islands, SIH and Sen. Cranston, 2/18/80
    - - H.R. 3757, Channel Islands, and Santa Barbara Channel, 2/18/80
    - - Porpoises/Man killed by shark, 8/25/80
    - - S. 3200, amendment to Clean Air Act, 11/14/80
    - - CA Rivers to National Wild and Scenic Rivers System, 11/14/80
    - - H.R. 7306, Lake Tahoe Basin, 12/4/80
    - - Congressional review and approval of proposed Wild and Scenic Rivers, 12/10/80
    - - S. 52, amend Clean Air Act, repeal requirement for inspection of automobiles, 1/6/81
    - - S. 522, CA Pacific Council, 2/20/81
    - - S. 842, RARE II Review Act of 1981, 3/31/81
    - - S. 875, Palo Verde Irrigation District, 4/2/81
    - - Article regarding Sierra Club, 5/11/81
    - - Treaty w/Canada on Pacific Coast Albacore Tuna Vessels, 7/20/81
    - - Santa Margarita, 6/28/82
    - - Trinity River, 8/4/82
    - - Tuolome River, 8/5/82
  - Foreign Relations
    - - SALT Negotiations, 3/3/78
    - - Lifting sanctions on Rhodesia, 6/28/78
    - - Rhodesia, 7/26/78
    - - Japanese Defense Policy, 7/26/78
    - - S. Res. 340, Andrei Sakharov, 1/28/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 72, UN Observers, Thailand & Cambodia border, 1/31/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 72, UN and Cambodian border, 2/19/80
    - - S. Res. 340, Andrei Sakharov, 2/19/80
    - - Flow of Iranians to US, 3/26/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 89, Liberia, 4/28/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 89, Liberia Resolution, 6/11/80
    - - S. 2727, Department of State authorization, 6/16/80
    - - S. 2422, International Development Cooperation, 6/16/80
    - - Human rights, 8/1/80
    - - Deportation of Iranians, 8/5/80
    - - Foreign Relations Article, 8/18/80
    - - S. 2437, American Sovereignty Protection Act, 8/19/80
    - - Iran Rally, 8/27/80
    - - Fuel to Iran, 9/24/80
    - - American Sovereignty Protection Act, 9/30/80
    - - Problems of Southern Africa, 9/30/80 (Box 29)
    - - Treatment of Christians in Soviet Union, 11/25/80
    - - H.R. 6942, International Security Development Assistance Conference Report, 12/3/80
    - - Southern Italy earthquake, 12/3/80
    - - S. Res. 562, Poland, 12/13/80
    - - Scuttled masses; refugees, 12/16/80
    - - S. 66, American Sovereignty Protection Act, 1/6/81
    - - Alexander M. Haig for Secretary of State, 1/21/81
    - - Comparison of Kirkpatrick to Sir K. Popper, 1/29/81
    - - Dr. J. Kirkpatrick as Ambassador to UN, 1/29/81
    - - S. 312, Soviet Pentacostals, 1/29/81
    - - Wm. Clark to be Deputy Secy. of State, 2/24/81
    - - S. Res. 103, Poland, 3/27/81
    - - International Military and Training Programs, 4/1/81
    - - "Trivialization of Human Rights", 4/1/81
    - - Dr. Chester Crocker - A Good Choice, 4/2/81
    - - Ernest Lefever, "A New Human Rights Champion", 4/8/81
    - - Ernest Lefever, "The Cambodian Blood Bath and the Great Silence", 4/9/81
    - - S. Res. 115, Collision of US sub and Japanese freighter, 4/9/81
    - - Dr. Lefever & the Administration's position on human rights, 5/11/81
    - - John H. Holdridge, Asst. Sec. of State for E. Asian Pacific Affairs, 5/19/81
    - - Nomination of Chester Crocker, Asst. Secy of State for African Affairs, 6/9/81
    - - Mr. Palmer to be Ambassador to Malaysia, 6/10/81
    - - Nomination of Charles Wick, Director, US International Communications Agency, 6/11/81
    - - Southeast Asian Aid - Thailand, 6/24/81
    - - Potential for Widespread Conflict, 7/15/81
    - - Standard deduction for charitable contributions, 7/20/81
    - - "The Source of Terrorism in Turkey, 7/30/81
    - - "What Can the Asia-Pacific Reg. Expect from the Nairobi Conference?", 7/30/81
    - - Address by Prime Minister Malcolm Fraser of Australia, "The Third World and the West", 8/3/81
    - - Business with China, 9/15/81
    - - ASEAN 14th Anniversary, 9/15/81
    - - The Peace Corps, 9/22/81
    - - ASEAN and Kampuchea, 9/25/81
    - - "America Looks to Asia with Moderate Interest", 9/30/81
    - - Death of Anwar Sadat, 10/7/81
    - - Soviet problems in Afghanistan, 10/14/81
    - - Arab Gulf Program, 10/19/81
    - - El Salvador, 11/5/81
    - - Cancun Summit Meeting, 11/21/81
    - - Consular Convention (PRC), 12/11/81
    - - Somalia, 3/15/82
    - - S. Con. Res. 84, relations between US and Korea, 4/29/82
    - - On Communicating with the Soviets, 5/12/82
    - - Thai Bicentennial, 5/21/82
    - - Peace Corps Volunteers, 6/17/82
    - - Letter from West Africa, 6/24/82
    - - Nomination of George Shultz, Secy. of State, 7/15/82
    - - Introduction of Korean Delegation of Parliament to Senate, 7/27/82
    - - President Chun's plan for Pacific summits, 9/27/82
    - - S. 1698, Amerasians, 9/28/82
    - - S. Res. 500, Zimbabwe Kidnapping, 12/3/82
    - - Polish Solidarity Day, 12/8/82
    - - S. Con. Res. 46, Mutual Security/US and Japan, 12/20/82
    - - Membership on Foreign Relations Committee, 12/23/82
  - Government Regulations
    - - Regulatory Reform, 7/27/77
    - - D.C. voting rights, 8/22/78
    - - Sunset legislation, 10/4/78
    - - S. 3204-07, election results, 11/18/80
    - - S. 55-58, provisions governing election of electors for President and Vice President, 1/6/81
    - - Nine digit Zip Code, 2/24/82
    - - The Regulatory Reform Act of 1981, 5/21/81
    - - Projecting Outcomes too soon (elections), 6/9/81
  - Health, Aging
    - - Saccharin Extension, 6/9/80
    - - Budget Reconciliation/day care, 6/30/80
    - - Teenage sex, 3/23/81
    - - National Physical Fitness and Sports For All Week, 4/1/81
    - - Prohibition Against Government Ban on Saccharin, 5/21/81
    - - S. 1377, refugee assistance, 6/25/81
    - - "Shriners Burn Prevention" campaign, 7/28/81
    - - Housing for the Elderly, 7/30/81
    - - Older Americans Opportunity Week, 9/11/81
    - - Older Americans Act, 11/2/81
    - - Voluntary Vitamins Act of 1981, 12/8/81
    - - Supplemental Appropriations - refugees, 8/10/82
  - Housing (Box 30)
    - - Housing Stimulus amendment, 5/27/82
    - - Lugar Housing amendment, 6/14/82
  - International Trade
    - - W. Brock as Special Trade Representative, 1/21/81
    - - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 9/30/81
    - - S. 2199, DISCs, 3/11/82
  - Judiciary
    - - S. 1647, Japanese-American Reparation, 5/22/80
    - - S. 2377, Department of Justice authorization, 6/18/80
    - - S. 2918, Leopoldine Schmid, 7/1/80
    - - Busing, 11/12/80
    - - Citizenship for Benjamin Bane, 11/25/80
    - - Busing amendment, 12/10/80
    - - Otay Mesa inspection station, 12/11/80
    - - S. Res. 21, commending James du Maresq Clavell, 1/6/81
    - - S. 53, Bilingual Ballots, amend voting rights act, 1/6/81
    - - "A Ballot Box Albatross", 1/27/81
    - - S. 521, private bill for Benjamin Bane, 2/20/81
    - - S. 930, Guest Worker Act of 1981, 4/8/81
    - - S. 930, Guest Worker Act of 1981, 4/9/81
    - - S.J. Res. 72, English as the official language, 4/27/81
    - - Pardoning of ex-FBI agents Felt and Miller, 4/30/81
    - - Wartime Relocation for civilians, 8/1/81
    - - Sandra O'Connor to be Associate US Supreme Court Judge, 9/21/81
    - - We All Lose This One (S.J. Res. 72), 10/14/81
    - - Adequate Prison Housing, 11/5/81
    - - Angel Island, 12/2/81
    - - S. 391, Intelligence Identities Act, 3/1/82
    - - "I'm Not Pregnant" (abortion), 4/1/82
    - - Litigiousness, 5/3/82
    - - American Youth Hostel Week, 5/6/82
    - - English Language Const. Amendment, S.J. Res. 72, 6/17/82
    - - Sex is not a spectator sport, 6/17/82
    - - Bilingual ballots, 6/18/82
    - - Vote against voting rights act extension, 6/18/82
    - - S. 1676, Motor Vehicle Theft Law Enforcement Act, 7/22/82
    - - Contributions of Japanese-Americans during World War II, 7/27/82
    - - Search warrant for INS, 8/13/82
    - - Immigration men must have warrant, 8/13/82
    - - English as official language, amendment #2019, 8/13/82
    - - S. Res. 451, Asylum for Hu Na, 8/18/82
    - - Public Debt Limit, abortion statement, 9/13/82
    - - S. 2572, crime, 10/1/82
    - - Hamburger crisis, 10/1/82
    - - Japanese-American reparations, 12/7/82
  - Labor
    - - Minimum Wage, 10/7/77
    - - Racism in American trade unions movement, 6/9/78
    - - Minimum wage increase, 8/25/78
    - - Lubbers nomination, NLRB, 4/16/80
    - - Lubbers nomination, NLRB, 4/17/80
    - - Zimmerman nomination, 8/5/80
    - - Minority firms, 9/25/80
    - - Affirmative Action, 9/30/81
    - - ERISA, 12/16/81
  - Miscellaneous
    - - Republican vs. Democratic parties, 7/28/77
    - - Sen. Moynihan's tribute to Sen. Hayakawa, 2/28/77
    - - National Mime Week, 3/29/79
    - - Tribute to Don Walsh, 1/23/80
    - - National Mime Week, 3/26/80
    - - S. 2337, Legal Services Corporation amendment, 6/13/80
    - - Award to Clifford Evans, 6/24/80
    - - Senior Citizens Internship Program, 7/28/80
    - - Tribute to Beatrice W. Hawkins, 8/20/80
    - - H.R. 7631, amendment #32, FEMA, 12/3/80
    - - S. Res. 100, honoring Joseph Rosenthal, 3/17/81
    - - "Creativity - the Human Resource", 5/11/81
    - - International Order of St. Hubert, 6/10/81
    - - A Sword, Legend are Going Home, 11/5/81
    - - Legal Services, 11/13/81
    - - Mr. Lyle J. Moore, 11/19/81
    - - Bill Muncey, 12/10/81
    - - Katela High School, 12/10/81
    - - Bruce T. Kaji, 2/3/82
    - - Trailside Murders solved, 2/11/82
    - - Steadfast service, 5/11/82
    - - "Ulysses" Goes Home, 6/17/82
    - - National Orchestra Week, 6/17/82
    - - New Baby Marks 6th Generation, 8/4/82
    - - Commendation of Myron Lee, 9/22/82
    - - Ross Davidson, 12/8/82
    - - Tribute to SIH, 12/82
  - Small Business (Box 31)
    - - S. 2221, Small Business Capital Gains Reduction Act, 1/24/80
    - - SBA (a) Program, government contracts, 9/25/80
    - - H.R. 6626, amendment regarding loan guarantees, 12/2/80
    - - Business Opportunity Fraud, 12/16/80
    - - Omnibus Small Business Capital Formation Act of 1981, 2/3/81
    - - S. 580, pollution control financing, 2/26/81
    - - Small Business Innovation Research Act, 4/8/81
    - - National Small Business Week, 5/10/81
    - - S.J. Res. 93, Competitive Enterprise System, 6/22/81
    - - "When Uncle Sam Goes into Business for Himself", 8/3/81
    - - H.R. 4169, Pollution Control Program Amendment, 11/12/81
    - - Small Business Representative on Federal Reserve Board, 12/8/81
    - - SBA Pollution Control Program, 12/10/81
    - - Small Business Procurement Act, 4/29/82
    - - Small Business Week, 5/11/82
    - - S. 1947, Small Business access to federal procurement info., 5/27/82
    - - Life and death of Paul R. Boucher, SBA, 7/19/82
    - - Small business innovation development act of 1982, 7/22/82
    - - Government relations and small business, 9/30/82
  - Social Security
    - - H.R. 3236, SSI - Aliens amendment, social security disabilities, 1/30/80
    - - H.R. 4331, restoring minimum social security benefits, 10/15/81
  - Taxes
    - - S. Res. 411, 15% withholding tax, 4/28/80
    - - H.R. 3317, wine amendment, 10/1/80
    - - H.R. 6806, public utilities, 12/16/80
    - - S. 232, amends IRS Code with respect to public utilities, 1/22/81
    - - S. 599, amends IRS Code by defining "artificial bait", 2/27/81
    - - Economic Recovery Tax Act of 1981, 7/16/81
    - - Commodity Straddle, 7/23/81
    - - S. 232, public property taxes, 7/27/81
    - - Tax vote, 8/1/81
    - - S. 2741, Ahmanson Foundation Tax Bill, 7/15/82
    - - H.R. 4961, UP 1155 mailing costs saving - H.R. 4961, interest withholding provisions - H.R. 4961, tax bill - H.R. 4981, fuel tax provisions, 7/22/82
    - - CA Utility Tax Amendment, 12/20/82
  - Transportation
    - MPH speed limit, 2/1/79-55
    - - S. 2696, National Ridesharing Act, 5/14/80
    - - S. Res. 101, Auto Industry resolution, 6/18/80
    - - H.R. 1197, Tonnage Measurement, 8/21/80
    - 9/18/80
      - DOT Approp/NHTSA
      - DOT Approp/Ridesharing
      - DOT Approp/55 MPH
    - 1/6/81
      - "Road and Track Report, May 1980"
      - S. 54, repeal National maximum speed limit
    - - San Francisco cable cars, 9/23/82
    - - NHTSA authorization and tire registration, 10/1/82
    - - DOT Santa Clara Project, 12/2/82
    - - 55 MPH, 12/8/82
    - - Temporary Matching Fund Waiver, 12/23/82
  - Agriculture
    - General
    - Advisory Council
    - Advisory Council, Fresno Constituency Council (Box 32)
    - Ag. Conference
    - Ag. Farm Mechanization
    - Almonds
    - Appropriatons, Agriculture
    - Appropriations
    - Aquaculture
    - Asparagus
    - Avocados
    - Beekeeper Indemnity Program
    - Block, John R.
    - Cash Out (Box 33)
    - C.F.T.C.
    - Census of Agriculture
    - Child Nutrition
    - Citrus
    - Cooperatives
    - Cotton Dust
    - Cotton Disaster
    - Credit
    - Cyclamates
    - Dairy
    - Dairy Standards (Box 34)
    - Department of Agriculture
    - Dietary Guidelines
    - Dutch Elm Disease
    - East Yolo Water District FmHa Application
    - E.D.B.
    - Family Farm Liberation Act
    - Fishing
    - F.I.F.R.A.
    - F.I.F.R.A. (Box 35)
    - Farm Bill
      - General
      - Dairy
      - Tobacco
      - Meat Labeling
      - Medfly
      - Peanuts
      - Sugar
    - Farm Credit Act Amendments (Box 36)
    - Farmers Home Administration
    - Farm Income
    - Farm Labor Contractor Act
    - Farm Protection Legislation
    - Federal Crop Insurance
    - Floral Research and Consumer Information Act
    - Floraboard
    - Food Stamps
    - Food Stamps (Box 37)
      - General
      - 97th Congress
    - Fruit and vegetable farms
    - Forest Service
    - G.A.T.T.
    - Bill Gillespie Base
    - Grain
    - Grain Embargo
    - Grain Standards Act
    - Good Letter File
    - Grapes (Box 38)
    - Grape Standards, S. 305
    - Gypsy Moth
    - Grasshoppers
    - Illegal Aliens
      - General
      - Old
    - Guest Worker Act of S. 930, 1982
    - Immigration, S. 2222
    - Lacey Act
    - Lettuce
    - Marijuana
    - Miscellaneous communications
    - Mexican American Good Neighbor Act
    - Medfly (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous
    - McAfee Case
    - Mushrooms
    - National Agriculture Day
    - Nutrition Labeling
    - Olives
    - Oranges Marketing Order
    - Peaches
    - Peanuts
    - Pilot Program
    - Pistachio
    - Predator Control
    - Press (Box 40)
    - Raisins
    - Reconciliation
    - Reconsituted milk
    - Reclamation
    - Reforestation
    - Revolving Fund
    - Rice sale to Korea
    - Rural Electrification Administration
    - Speeches
    - Trade with Japan
    - Transition, Reagan Administration
    - Tobacco
    - U.F.W.
      - General
      - Grants (Box 41)
    - Wine Grape Growers
  - Budget, Taxes
    - SIH reaction to "Program for Economic Recovery,", 2/18/81
    - SIH legislation package, 1918
    - S. 599, Artificial bait
    - Fed. Vice Chair
    - Program for Economic Recovery, 4/18/81
    - Budget Act Process
    - Budget Statistics
    - Flat Tax Rate
    - CPI, general (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous economy/inflation
    - Rep. Jack Kemp
    - David Stockman
    - S.J. Res. 58, Balanced Budget
    - FY Budget, 1983
    - Tax Bill, 1982 (Box 43)
    - H.J. Res. 370, Further continuing appropriations FY, 1982
    - S. Con. Res. 50, Second Concurrent Resolution, 1982
    - Reconciliation
    - H.J. Res. 520, Debt Limit
    - Debt limit extension
    - H.J. Res. 265, Debt Limit
    - S. Con. Res. 119/H. Con. Res. 448, 2nd Concurrent Budget Resolution
    - H.R. 6211, Highway/gas tax bill
    - Pacific Telephone Utility Tax Normalization (Box 44)
    - California Utility Tax Bill (Box 45)
    - Enterprise Zones (Box 46)
    - Franzia Stock options
    - Pollution Control
    - Ingredient Labeling, alcohol (Box 47)
    - Budget Advisory Council
  - International Trade
    - Miscellaneous special projects
    - S. 734, Exporting Trade Co. (Box 48)
    - SIH statements, international trade
    - Advisory Committee correspondence
    - Exports
    - IT/Export Caucus
    - Trade/hides
    - TR/MFN, Romania
    - Roses, import tariffs
    - Whaling
  - Taxes (Box 49)
    - S. 408, Foreign Earned Income
    - S. 31. Armstrong, Home Deduction
    - Members' tax deductions
    - Finance Committee, 97th Congress
    - S. 1406, Usury
    - S. 578, Moynihan, "Thor"
    - S. 626, Moynihan, commodity tax straddles
    - Tuition tax credits
    - S. 655, Unitary tax
    - S. 850, Taxpayer's Bill of Rights (Box 50)
    - S. 889, 1162, Long, ESOP
    - Jensen, Laxalt, Family Protection Act
    - S. 1607, D'Amato, 200/400
    - S. 2281, Danforth, Apple Comp.
    - Agricultural withholding
    - Continental Development Building, S.F. Ferry Building
    - Disabled Employees Rehabilitation Inc.
    - Four Phase
    - Gordon Enterprises
    - Dan Belknap
    - Richard Putney
    - W. Clement Stone Insurance
    - Misc. special projects
    - Soule Steel
    - S. 1619, Film Tax Credits - Training
    - S. 2, Mathias "Marriage Tax"
    - S. Con. Res. 12, Action on Reagan Econ. Plan by, May 31
    - S. 287, Heinz, Capital Cost Revovery Act
    - S. 360, Small Business Tax Bill
    - S. 395, Wallop Estate/Gift Tax
    - S. 683, Administration Tax Package
    - S. 940, Thurmond, UCLA, Film, Fox, U South Carolina
    - Roth-Kemp II (S. 33 & 34)
    - S. 100 - Reforestation
    - S. 103 - IRS regulation of private schools
    - S. 208 - Internal Revenue - Foreign investors and capital gains
    - S. 224 - Regulations on the taxation of fringe benefits
    - S. 589 - Foreign conventions
    - S. 873 - Overseas Residency Taxes
    - S. 326, 955 - Taxpayer's Bill of Rights
    - S. 1163 - "Carryover" repeal
    - S. 1597 - Economic stimulus (Box 51)
    - S. 2226 - Heads of households
    - S. 2547 - Bottling
    - S. 1964, 2924 - Rollover accounts
    - S. 2221, 2983 - Capital gains
    - S. 2878 - Tax package
    - S. 1695 - Generation-Skipping
    - S. Res. 411
    - S. 1645 - Tax Credit for Interest
    - S. 2239 - Stock options
  - Economy
    - Dollar
    - Electronic Fund Transfer
    - Emergency Banking Deregulation
    - Fairness Doctrine
    - F.I.R.E. Group
    - Financial Institutions Reform
    - Federal Reserve Membership
    - Banks Foreign Ownership
    - DIDC, Depository Institutions Deregulation Committee
    - S. 1424, Money Market Mutual Fund Bill
    - Mortgage
    - DITI
    - Reverse Mortgages
    - Monetary Control Act
    - Interstate Branching
    - Interest rates
    - Due-on-Sale clauses
    - Mutual funds
  - Taxes (Box 52)
    - Advanced earned income credit
    - Agricultural withholding
    - Tax deductions - auto
    - Hansen-Steiger, S. 3065 Capital gains
    - Above the Line Charitable Contributions Deduction
    - Commodity Straddle
    - Debt-Equity Regulations
    - Double Taxation of Dividends
    - Dividend reinvestment - utility
    - Earned income abroad
    - Mortgage subsidy bonds
    - Economic Recovery Tax Act of, 1981
    - Excise taxes
    - Tax exempt organizations - churches
    - Tax exempt bonds
    - Foreign conventions
    - Taxation of fringe benefits
    - Independent contractors
    - Dole, indexing
    - IRAs (Box 53)
    - Inheritance taxes
    - Interest deductions for indebtedness
    - Small business participating
    - IRS private schools and labor
    - IRS regulations on lobbying influence
    - Tax exempt mortgage bonds
    - Proposition 13
    - Sick pay regulations
    - S. 1412, D'Amato State Legislators
    - Taxation of interest/deductions
    - Tax cut package H.R. 5829
    - Travel deductions, mileage
    - Underground, economy
    - Windfall profits
    - Value-added tax
    - S. 1913, wine excise tax
  - Banking (Box 54)
    - S. 207, Bank Holding Company Act
    - S. 1230, Olympic Gold Coin Act
    - Consumer Coop Bank correspondence
    - National Consumer Coop
    - C.T. Conover, Comptroller of Currency
    - Susan B. Anthony dollar
    - Credit cards
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - S. 414, Cash Discount Act
    - Banking consumer credit (Box 55)
    - Central banking
    - Credit - general
    - Deregulation
    - Savings and loans issues
    - H.R. 1539, underwrite municipal revenue bonds